For king. For country. For brotherhood.
Battle Over Britain is a war film directed by Callum Burn.
A young pilot, fresh out of training, is called to join a
Flight while they wait for the call to scramble.
Throughout a single day, he witnesses the skies of southern England filled with deadly dog fights, and after every
exhausting battle the men return to their dispersal hut, only to find another of their number missing.
Unwilling to surrender, the pilot and his comrades unite to take to the skies once more,
determined to defend not only the airfield, but their entire country.
Andrew Sharp, played by Arnold Voysey.
Nathan Walker, played by Vin Hawke.
Nancy White, played by Hannah Harris.
Laurence Stanhope, played by Chris Clynes.
Michael Cochrane, played by Tom Gordon.
Richard Cooper, played by Micky David.
Boudica (or sometimes Boudica: Queen of War), is a 2023 British
action drama film directed and written by Jesse V.
The film follows the eponymous Celtic warrior of the Iceni people, Boudica, in Roman Britain and
how she revolted against the Romans after the death of her husband, Prasutagus.
The film stars Olga Kurylenko as the titular character.
The film received mixed reviews.
The film explores themes of world war ii, 1940s,
1930s, battle of britain, luftwaffe.